- [Narrator] Every person
on Facebook is unique.
In fact, there are billions
of people on Facebook
spread across countries,
continents, and cultures,
and no two are alike.
So it only makes sense that
the service Facebook offers
is a completely personalized experience
based on all the things
that make you, well, you.
To do this, we use
information to learn more
about the things you might be into.
This information is based
on a number of sources,
like how you use our products,
and it helps us create
a Facebook experience
that is built around your interests.
For example, we might use
the location you've set
as your hometown on Facebook
to recommend a local
group for you to join.
Or if we see that you liked
some South Asian food Pages,
we might suggest some specialty stores
or cookware retailers in your area.
Your information also helps us
to provide a safer experience
for everyone using Meta
products and devices.
This includes protecting
others on Facebook
by monitoring for harmful content.
We also use your information
to improve your experience,
like by making sure content is shown
in a language that's
common in your location
or helping you grow your circle
by suggesting new connections.
You can manage your information
through a number of privacy controls,
including Ad Preferences,
Off-Facebook Activity,
and Privacy Checkup.
When it comes to your
information, we're here for you,
and helping you understand
how your information is collected, used,
and shared is our responsibility.
So whether you're messaging, posting,
shopping, liking, or
sharing, we're committed
to helping you have the
best experience possible
across all of our apps and products.